You're not going to believe this, but my robot dog is finally alive.
你不会相信的 但我的机器人狗终于还活着
Wave to the audience, would ya?
向观众挥手,好吗?
Oh my gosh, dude.
哦,我的天哪,伙计。
Sit down.
请坐
Aww.
呵呵。
I told you guys the top comment would name it whatever you wanted.
我告诉过你们 最顶尖的评语会命名它 任何你想要的。
With over 14,000 likes, you guys picked Foam.
超过14000个喜欢的人, 你们选了泡沫。
F-O-A-M.
F -O -A
Now, the only question I have for you guys now,
现在我唯一要问的就是你们
because I did, in fact, name him Foam.
因为我确实给他取了福阿姆的名字
What do you think Foam should stand for?
你认为泡沫应该代表什么?
I wanted to see what he was actually capable of,
我想看看他到底能干些什么
so I took him in my living room.
所以我带他进客厅
I pet him, and then, yeah, I kicked him, okay?
我抚摸他,然后,是的,我踢了他,好吗?
But it was for science.
但它是为了科学。
Then I pushed him, but don't worry, he's fine.
然后我推他,但别担心,他没事
He might even like it, weirdly.
他甚至可能喜欢它,怪怪的。
He's way tougher than it looks, but he's probably plotting revenge.
他比看起来要坚强得多 但他可能正在策划报复
Now I introduced Foam to my actual dog, and that was a mistake.
现在我把泡沫介绍给我的狗, 那是个错误。
Apparently, my dog thinks Foam is a threat to national security.
显然 我的狗认为福阿姆是对国家安全的威胁
I think my dog hates him, but honestly, I kind of get it.
我想我的狗恨他,但说实话,我有点懂了
And then Foam tried to assert dominance by jumping at her.
然后Foam试图通过跳跃她来维护主导地位。
He can do so many different things, like even climb,
他可以做很多不同的事情, 比如攀登,
but I haven't even tried that yet.
但我还没试过
Let me know what else in the comments you want to see me do.
让我知道,在评论中,你还想看到我做什么。